[
{"Front": "会う", "Back": "to meet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "青", "Back": "blue", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "青い", "Back": "blue", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "赤", "Back": "red", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "赤い", "Back": "red", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "明い", "Back": "bright", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "秋", "Back": "autumn", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "開く", "Back": "to open,to become open", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "開ける", "Back": "to open", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "上げる", "Back": "to give", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "朝", "Back": "morning", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "朝御飯", "Back": "breakfast", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あさって", "Back": "day after tomorrow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "足", "Back": "foot,leg", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "明日", "Back": "tomorrow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あそこ", "Back": "over there", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "遊ぶ", "Back": "to play,to make a visit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "暖かい", "Back": "warm", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "頭", "Back": "head", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "新しい", "Back": "new", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あちら", "Back": "there", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "暑い", "Back": "hot", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "熱い", "Back": "hot to the touch", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "厚い", "Back": "kind, deep, thick", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あっち", "Back": "over there", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "後", "Back": "afterwards", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あなた", "Back": "you", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "兄", "Back": "(humble) older brother", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "姉", "Back": "(humble) older sister", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あの", "Back": "that over there", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "アパート", "Back": "apartment", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あびる", "Back": "to bathe,to shower", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "危ない", "Back": "dangerous", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "甘い", "Back": "sweet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あまり", "Back": "not very", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "雨", "Back": "rain", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "飴", "Back": "candy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "洗う", "Back": "to wash", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ある", "Back": "to be,to have (used for inanimate objects)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "歩く", "Back": "to walk", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "あれ", "Back": "that", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いい/よい", "Back": "good", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いいえ", "Back": "no", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "言う", "Back": "to say", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "家", "Back": "house", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いかが", "Back": "how", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "行く", "Back": "to go", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いくつ", "Back": "how many?,how old?", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いくら", "Back": "how much?", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "池", "Back": "pond", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "医者", "Back": "medical doctor", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いす", "Back": "chair", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "忙しい", "Back": "busy,irritated", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "痛い", "Back": "painful", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一", "Back": "one", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一日", "Back": "(1) one day, (2) first of month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いちばん", "Back": "best,first", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いつ", "Back": "when", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "五日", "Back": "five days, fifth day", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一緒", "Back": "together", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "五つ", "Back": "five", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いつも", "Back": "always", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "犬", "Back": "dog", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今", "Back": "now", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "意味", "Back": "meaning", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "妹", "Back": "(humble) younger sister", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "嫌", "Back": "unpleasant", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "入口", "Back": "entrance", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "居る", "Back": "to be, to have (used for people and animals)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "要る", "Back": "to need", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "入れる", "Back": "to put in", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "色", "Back": "colour", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "いろいろ", "Back": "various", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "上", "Back": "on top of", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "後ろ", "Back": "behind", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "薄い", "Back": "thin,weak", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "歌", "Back": "song", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "歌う", "Back": "to sing", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "生まれる", "Back": "to be born", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "海", "Back": "sea", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "売る", "Back": "to sell", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "煩い", "Back": "noisy,annoying", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "上着", "Back": "jacket", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "絵", "Back": "picture", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "映画", "Back": "movie", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "映画館", "Back": "cinema", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "英語", "Back": "English language", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ええ", "Back": "yes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "駅", "Back": "station", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "エレベーター", "Back": "elevator", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "鉛筆", "Back": "pencil", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おいしい", "Back": "delicious", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "多い", "Back": "many", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大きい", "Back": "big", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大きな", "Back": "big", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大勢", "Back": "great number of people", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お母さん", "Back": "(honorable) mother", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お菓子", "Back": "sweets, candy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お金", "Back": "money", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "起きる", "Back": "to get up", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "置く", "Back": "to put", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "奥さん", "Back": "(honorable) wife", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お酒", "Back": "alcohol, rice wine", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お皿", "Back": "plate, dish", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "伯父/叔父", "Back": "grandfather,male senior citizen", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "教える", "Back": "to teach,to tell", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "押す", "Back": "to push, to stamp something", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "遅い", "Back": "late,slow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お茶", "Back": "green tea", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お手洗い", "Back": "bathroom", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お父さん", "Back": "(honorable) father", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "弟", "Back": "younger brother", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "男", "Back": "man", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "男の子", "Back": "boy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一昨日", "Back": "day before yesterday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一昨年", "Back": "year before last", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大人", "Back": "adult", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おなか", "Back": "stomach", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "同じ", "Back": "same", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お兄さん", "Back": "(honorable) older brother", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お姉さん", "Back": "(honorable) older sister", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おばあさん", "Back": "grandmother,female senior-citizen", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "伯母さん/叔母さん", "Back": "aunt", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お風呂", "Back": "bath", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "お弁当", "Back": "boxed lunch", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "覚える", "Back": "to remember", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おまわりさん", "Back": "friendly term for policeman", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "重い", "Back": "heavy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "おもしろい", "Back": "interesting", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "泳ぐ", "Back": "to swim", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "降りる", "Back": "to get off, to descend", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "終る", "Back": "to finish", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "音楽", "Back": "music", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "女", "Back": "woman", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "女の子", "Back": "girl", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "外国", "Back": "foreign country", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "外国人", "Back": "foreigner", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "会社", "Back": "company", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "階段", "Back": "stairs", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "買い物", "Back": "shopping", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "買う", "Back": "to buy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "返す", "Back": "to return something", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "帰る", "Back": "to go back", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "かかる", "Back": "to take time or money", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "かぎ", "Back": "key", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "書く", "Back": "to write", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "学生", "Back": "student", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "かける", "Back": "to call by phone", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "傘", "Back": "umbrella", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "貸す", "Back": "to lend", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "風", "Back": "wind", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "風邪", "Back": "a cold", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "家族", "Back": "family", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "方", "Back": "person, way of doing", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "学校", "Back": "school", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "カップ", "Back": "cup", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "家庭", "Back": "household", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "角", "Back": "a corner", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "かばん", "Back": "bag,basket", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "花瓶", "Back": "a vase", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "紙", "Back": "paper", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "カメラ", "Back": "camera", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "火曜日", "Back": "Tuesday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "辛い", "Back": "spicy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "体", "Back": "body", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "借りる", "Back": "to borrow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "軽い", "Back": "light", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "カレー", "Back": "curry", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "カレンダー", "Back": "calendar", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "川/河", "Back": "river", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "かわいい", "Back": "cute", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "漢字", "Back": "Chinese character", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "木", "Back": "tree,wood", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "黄色", "Back": "yellow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "黄色い", "Back": "yellow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "消える", "Back": "to disappear", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "聞く", "Back": "to hear,to listen to,to ask", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "北", "Back": "north", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ギター", "Back": "guitar", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "汚い", "Back": "dirty", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "喫茶店", "Back": "coffee lounge", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "切手", "Back": "postage stamp", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "切符", "Back": "ticket", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "昨日", "Back": "yesterday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "九", "Back": "nine", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "牛肉", "Back": "beef", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "牛乳", "Back": "milk", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今日", "Back": "today", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "教室", "Back": "classroom", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "兄弟", "Back": "(humble) siblings", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "去年", "Back": "last year", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "嫌い", "Back": "hate", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "切る", "Back": "to cut", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "着る", "Back": "to put on from the shoulders down", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "きれい", "Back": "pretty,clean", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "キロ/キログラム", "Back": "kilogram", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "キロ/キロメートル", "Back": "kilometre", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "銀行", "Back": "bank", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "金曜日", "Back": "Friday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "薬", "Back": "medicine", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ください", "Back": "please", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "果物", "Back": "fruit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "口", "Back": "mouth,opening", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "靴", "Back": "shoes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "靴下", "Back": "socks", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "国", "Back": "country", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "曇り", "Back": "cloudy weather", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "曇る", "Back": "to become cloudy,to become dim", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "暗い", "Back": "gloomy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "クラス", "Back": "class", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "グラム", "Back": "gram", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "来る", "Back": "to come", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "車", "Back": "car,vehicle", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "黒", "Back": "black", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "黒い", "Back": "black", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "警官", "Back": "policeman", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今朝", "Back": "this morning", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "消す", "Back": "to erase,to turn off power", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "結構", "Back": "splendid,enough", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "結婚", "Back": "marriage", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "月曜日", "Back": "Monday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "玄関", "Back": "entry hall", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "元気", "Back": "health, vitality", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "五", "Back": "five", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "公園", "Back": "park", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "交差点", "Back": "intersection", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "紅茶", "Back": "black tea", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "交番", "Back": "police box", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "声", "Back": "voice", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "コート", "Back": "coat,tennis court", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "コーヒー", "Back": "coffee", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ここ", "Back": "here", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "午後", "Back": "afternoon", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "九日", "Back": "nine days, ninth day", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "九つ", "Back": "nine", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "午前", "Back": "morning", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "答える", "Back": "to answer", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "こちら", "Back": "this person or way", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "こっち", "Back": "this person or way", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "コップ", "Back": "a glass", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今年", "Back": "this year", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "言葉", "Back": "word,language", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "子供", "Back": "child", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "この", "Back": "this", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "御飯", "Back": "cooked rice,meal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "コピーする", "Back": "to copy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "困る", "Back": "to be worried", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "これ", "Back": "this", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今月", "Back": "this month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今週", "Back": "this week", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "こんな", "Back": "such", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "今晩", "Back": "this evening", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "さあ", "Back": "well…", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "財布", "Back": "wallet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "魚", "Back": "fish", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "先", "Back": "the future,previous", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "咲く", "Back": "to bloom", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "作文", "Back": "composition,writing", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "差す", "Back": "to stretch out hands,to raise an umbrella", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "雑誌", "Back": "magazine", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "砂糖", "Back": "sugar", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "寒い", "Back": "cold", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "さ来年", "Back": "year after next", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "三", "Back": "three", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "散歩", "Back": "to stroll", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "四", "Back": "four", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "塩", "Back": "salt", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "しかし", "Back": "however", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "時間", "Back": "time", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "仕事", "Back": "job", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "辞書", "Back": "dictionary", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "静か", "Back": "quiet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "下", "Back": "below", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "七", "Back": "seven", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "質問", "Back": "question", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "自転車", "Back": "bicycle", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "自動車", "Back": "automobile", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "死ぬ", "Back": "to die", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "字引", "Back": "dictionary", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "自分", "Back": "oneself", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "閉まる", "Back": "to close,to be closed", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "閉める", "Back": "to close something", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "締める", "Back": "to tie", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "じゃ/じゃあ", "Back": "well then…", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "写真", "Back": "photograph", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "シャツ", "Back": "shirt", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "シャワー", "Back": "shower", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "十", "Back": "ten", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "授業", "Back": "lesson,class work", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "宿題", "Back": "homework", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "上手", "Back": "skillful", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "丈夫", "Back": "strong,durable", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "しょうゆ", "Back": "soy sauce", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "食堂", "Back": "dining hall", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "知る", "Back": "to know", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "白", "Back": "white", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "白い", "Back": "white", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "新聞", "Back": "newspaper", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "水曜日", "Back": "Wednesday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "吸う", "Back": "to smoke,to suck", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "スカート", "Back": "skirt", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "好き", "Back": "likeable", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "少ない", "Back": "a few", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "すぐに", "Back": "instantly", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "少し", "Back": "few", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "涼しい", "Back": "refreshing", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ストーブ", "Back": "heater", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "スプーン", "Back": "spoon", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "スポーツ", "Back": "sport", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ズボン", "Back": "trousers", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "住む", "Back": "to live in", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "スリッパ", "Back": "slippers", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "する", "Back": "to do", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "座る", "Back": "to sit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "背", "Back": "height,stature", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "生徒", "Back": "pupil", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "セーター", "Back": "sweater,jumper", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "せっけん", "Back": "economy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "背広", "Back": "business suit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "狭い", "Back": "narrow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ゼロ", "Back": "zero", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "千", "Back": "thousand", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "先月", "Back": "last month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "先週", "Back": "last week", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "先生", "Back": "teacher,doctor", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "洗濯", "Back": "washing", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "全部", "Back": "all", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "掃除", "Back": "to clean, to sweep", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そうして/そして", "Back": "and", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そこ", "Back": "that place", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そちら", "Back": "over there", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そっち", "Back": "over there", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "外", "Back": "outside", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "その", "Back": "that", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "そば", "Back": "near,beside", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "空", "Back": "sky", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "それ", "Back": "that", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "それから", "Back": "after that", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "それでは", "Back": "in that situation", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大学", "Back": "university", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大使館", "Back": "embassy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大丈夫", "Back": "all right", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大好き", "Back": "to be very likeable", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "大切", "Back": "important", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "台所", "Back": "kitchen", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "たいへん", "Back": "very", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "高い", "Back": "tall, expensive", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "たくさん", "Back": "many", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "タクシー", "Back": "taxi", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "出す", "Back": "to put out", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "立つ", "Back": "to stand", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "たて", "Back": "length,height", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "建物", "Back": "building", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "楽しい", "Back": "enjoyable", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "頼む", "Back": "to ask", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "たぶん", "Back": "probably", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "たばこ", "Back": "tobacco,cigarettes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "食べ物", "Back": "food", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "食べる", "Back": "to eat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "卵", "Back": "egg", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "誰", "Back": "who", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "誕生日", "Back": "birthday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "だんだん", "Back": "gradually", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "小さい", "Back": "little", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "小さな", "Back": "little", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "近い", "Back": "near", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "違う", "Back": "to differ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "近く", "Back": "near", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "地下鉄", "Back": "underground train", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "地図", "Back": "map", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "茶色", "Back": "brown", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ちゃわん", "Back": "rice bowl", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ちょうど", "Back": "exactly", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ちょっと", "Back": "somewhat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "使う", "Back": "to use", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "疲れる", "Back": "to get tired", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "次", "Back": "next", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "着く", "Back": "to arrive at", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "机", "Back": "desk", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "作る", "Back": "to make", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "つける", "Back": "to turn on", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "勤める", "Back": "to work for someone", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "つまらない", "Back": "boring", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "冷たい", "Back": "cold to the touch", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "強い", "Back": "powerful", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "手", "Back": "hand", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "テープ", "Back": "tape", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "テーブル", "Back": "table", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "テープレコーダー", "Back": "tape recorder", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "出かける", "Back": "to go out", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "手紙", "Back": "letter", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "できる", "Back": "to be able to", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "出口", "Back": "exit", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "テスト", "Back": "test", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "では", "Back": "with that...", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "デパート", "Back": "department store", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "でも", "Back": "but", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "出る", "Back": "to appear,to leave", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "テレビ", "Back": "television", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "天気", "Back": "weather", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "電気", "Back": "electricity,electric light", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "電車", "Back": "electric train", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "電話", "Back": "telephone", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "戸", "Back": "Japanese style door", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ドア", "Back": "Western style door", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "トイレ", "Back": "toilet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どう", "Back": "how,in what way", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どうして", "Back": "for what reason", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どうぞ", "Back": "please", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "動物", "Back": "animal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どうも", "Back": "thanks", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "遠い", "Back": "far", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "十日", "Back": "ten days,the tenth day", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "時々", "Back": "sometimes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "時計", "Back": "watch,clock", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どこ", "Back": "where", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "所", "Back": "place", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "年", "Back": "year", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "図書館", "Back": "library", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どちら", "Back": "which of two", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どっち", "Back": "which", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "とても", "Back": "very", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どなた", "Back": "who", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "隣", "Back": "next door to", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どの", "Back": "which", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "飛ぶ", "Back": "to fly,to hop", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "止まる", "Back": "to come to a halt", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "友達", "Back": "friend", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "土曜日", "Back": "Saturday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "鳥", "Back": "bird", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "とり肉", "Back": "chicken meat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "取る", "Back": "to take something", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "撮る", "Back": "to take a photo or record a film", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "どれ", "Back": "which (of three or more)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ナイフ", "Back": "knife", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "中", "Back": "middle", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "長い", "Back": "long", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "鳴く", "Back": "animal noise. to chirp, roar or croak etc.", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "無くす", "Back": "to lose something", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "なぜ", "Back": "why", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "夏", "Back": "summer", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "夏休み", "Back": "summer holiday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "など", "Back": "et cetera", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "七つ", "Back": "seven", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "七日", "Back": "seven days,the seventh day", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "名前", "Back": "name", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "習う", "Back": "to learn", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "並ぶ", "Back": "to line up,to stand in a line", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "並べる", "Back": "to line up,to set up", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "なる", "Back": "to become", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "何", "Back": "what", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "二", "Back": "two", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "賑やか", "Back": "bustling,busy", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "肉", "Back": "meat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "西", "Back": "west", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "日曜日", "Back": "Sunday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "荷物", "Back": "luggage", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ニュース", "Back": "news", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "庭", "Back": "garden", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "脱ぐ", "Back": "to take off clothes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "温い", "Back": "luke warm", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ネクタイ", "Back": "tie,necktie", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "猫", "Back": "cat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "寝る", "Back": "to go to bed,to sleep", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ノート", "Back": "notebook,exercise book", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "登る", "Back": "to climb", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "飲み物", "Back": "a drink", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "飲む", "Back": "to drink", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "乗る", "Back": "to get on,to ride", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "歯", "Back": "tooth", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "パーティー", "Back": "party", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "はい", "Back": "yes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "灰皿", "Back": "ashtray", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "入る", "Back": "to enter,to contain", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "葉書", "Back": "postcard", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "はく", "Back": "to wear,to put on trousers", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "箱", "Back": "box", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "橋", "Back": "bridge", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "はし", "Back": "chopsticks", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "始まる", "Back": "to begin", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "初め/始め", "Back": "beginning", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "初めて", "Back": "for the first time", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "走る", "Back": "to run", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "バス", "Back": "bus", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "バター", "Back": "butter", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "二十歳", "Back": "20 years old,20th year", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "働く", "Back": "to work", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "八", "Back": "eight", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "二十日", "Back": "twenty days,twentieth", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "花", "Back": "flower", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "鼻", "Back": "nose", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "話", "Back": "talk,story", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "話す", "Back": "to speak", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "早い", "Back": "early", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "速い", "Back": "quick", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "春", "Back": "spring", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "貼る", "Back": "to stick", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "晴れ", "Back": "clear weather", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "晴れる", "Back": "to be sunny", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "半", "Back": "half", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "晩", "Back": "evening", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "パン", "Back": "bread", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ハンカチ", "Back": "handkerchief", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "番号", "Back": "number", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "晩御飯", "Back": "evening meal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "半分", "Back": "half minute", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "東", "Back": "east", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "引く", "Back": "to pull", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "弾く", "Back": "to play an instrument with strings, including piano", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "低い", "Back": "short,low", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "飛行機", "Back": "aeroplane", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "左", "Back": "left hand side", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "人", "Back": "person", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一つ", "Back": "one", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一月", "Back": "one month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "一人", "Back": "one person", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "暇", "Back": "free time", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "百", "Back": "hundred", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "病院", "Back": "hospital", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "病気", "Back": "illness", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "昼", "Back": "noon, daytime", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "昼御飯", "Back": "midday meal", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "広い", "Back": "spacious,wide", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "フィルム", "Back": "roll of film", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "封筒", "Back": "envelope", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "プール", "Back": "swimming pool", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "フォーク", "Back": "fork", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "吹く", "Back": "to blow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "服", "Back": "clothes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "二つ", "Back": "two", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "豚肉", "Back": "pork", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "二人", "Back": "two people", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "二日", "Back": "two days, second day of the month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "太い", "Back": "fat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "冬", "Back": "winter", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "降る", "Back": "to fall, e.g. rain or snow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "古い", "Back": "old (not used for people)", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ふろ", "Back": "bath", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "文章", "Back": "sentence,text", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ページ", "Back": "page", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "下手", "Back": "unskillful", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ベッド", "Back": "bed", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ペット", "Back": "pet", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "部屋", "Back": "room", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "辺", "Back": "area", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ペン", "Back": "pen", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "勉強", "Back": "to study", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "便利", "Back": "useful, convenient", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "帽子", "Back": "hat", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ボールペン", "Back": "ball-point pen", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ほか", "Back": "other, the rest", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ポケット", "Back": "pocket", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "欲しい", "Back": "want", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ポスト", "Back": "post", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "細い", "Back": "thin", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ボタン", "Back": "button", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ホテル", "Back": "hotel", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "本", "Back": "book", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "本棚", "Back": "bookshelves", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ほんとう", "Back": "truth", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "毎朝", "Back": "every morning", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "毎月", "Back": "every month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "毎週", "Back": "every week", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "毎日", "Back": "every day", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "毎年", "Back": "every year", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "毎晩", "Back": "every night", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "前", "Back": "before", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "曲る", "Back": "to turn,to bend", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "まずい", "Back": "unpleasant", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "また", "Back": "again,and", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "まだ", "Back": "yet,still", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "町", "Back": "town,city", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "待つ", "Back": "to wait", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "まっすぐ", "Back": "straight ahead,direct", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "マッチ", "Back": "match", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "窓", "Back": "window", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "丸い/円い", "Back": "round,circular", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "万", "Back": "ten thousand", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "万年筆", "Back": "fountain pen", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "磨く", "Back": "to brush teeth, to polish", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "右", "Back": "right side", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "短い", "Back": "short", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "水", "Back": "water", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "店", "Back": "shop", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "見せる", "Back": "to show", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "道", "Back": "street", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "三日", "Back": "three days, third day of the month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "三つ", "Back": "three", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "緑", "Back": "green", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "皆さん", "Back": "everyone", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "南", "Back": "south", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "耳", "Back": "ear", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "見る&nbsp;&nbsp;観る", "Back": "to see, to watch", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "みんな", "Back": "everyone", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "六日", "Back": "six days, sixth day of the month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "向こう", "Back": "over there", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "難しい", "Back": "difficult", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "六つ", "Back": "six", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "村", "Back": "village", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "目", "Back": "eye", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "メートル", "Back": "metre", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "眼鏡", "Back": "glasses", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "もう", "Back": "already", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "もう一度", "Back": "again", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "木曜日", "Back": "Thursday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "持つ", "Back": "to hold", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "もっと", "Back": "more", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "物", "Back": "thing", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "門", "Back": "gate", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "問題", "Back": "problem", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "八百屋", "Back": "greengrocer", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "野菜", "Back": "vegetable", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "易しい", "Back": "easy, simple", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "安い", "Back": "cheap", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "休み", "Back": "rest,holiday", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "休む", "Back": "to rest", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "八つ", "Back": "eight", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "山", "Back": "mountain", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "やる", "Back": "to do", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "夕方", "Back": "evening", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "夕飯", "Back": "dinner", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "郵便局", "Back": "post office", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "昨夜", "Back": "last night", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "有名", "Back": "famous", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "雪", "Back": "snow", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ゆっくりと", "Back": "slowly", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "八日", "Back": "eight days, eighth day of the month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "洋服", "Back": "western-style clothes", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "よく", "Back": "often, well", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "横", "Back": "beside,side,width", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "四日", "Back": "four days, fouth day of the month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "四つ", "Back": "four", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "呼ぶ", "Back": "to call out,to invite", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "読む", "Back": "to read", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "夜", "Back": "evening,night", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "弱い", "Back": "weak", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "来月", "Back": "next month", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "来週", "Back": "next week", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "来年", "Back": "next year", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ラジオ", "Back": "radio", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ラジカセ / ラジオカセット", "Back": "radio cassette player", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "りっぱ", "Back": "splendid", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "留学生", "Back": "overseas student", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "両親", "Back": "both parents", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "料理", "Back": "cuisine", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "旅行", "Back": "travel", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "零", "Back": "zero", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "冷蔵庫", "Back": "refrigerator", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "レコード", "Back": "record", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "レストラン", "Back": "restaurant", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "練習", "Back": "to practice", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "廊下", "Back": "corridor", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "六", "Back": "six", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "ワイシャツ", "Back": "business shirt", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "若い", "Back": "young", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "分かる", "Back": "to be understood", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "忘れる", "Back": "to forget", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "私", "Back": "(humble) I,myself", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "渡す", "Back": "to hand over", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "渡る", "Back": "to go across", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "悪い", "Back": "bad", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{"Front": "より、ほう", "Back": "Used for comparison.", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-eng"},
{}]
